Now, we are going to be talking about tennis balls; a very important part of tennis.
I'm going to give you an example of a good tennis ball.
This would be a decent tennis ball.
It has hair; you can see the logo of it pretty clear.
This would be an example of a bad tennis ball.
The ball is almost pretty much gone, you can see the logo is almost gone, the yellow color of it is also gone and most important you can squeeze it and it's almost going to go all the way down, as you can see right here.
When a good tennis ball you can squeeze it, but it will stay firm on your hand.
Where to place your tennis balls?
That's a very important question.
I'll bet all of you are going to be serving and that's where your outfit comes in.
You want to have a tennis cap to protect you from the sun.
You want to make sure you put sunscreen to protect you from the sun.
You want to make sure you have pants or skirt where you can put your balls.
For example today I have a skirt that is also a; it has pants and it has a skirt so I can actually put my ball inside a small pocket that is right here.
There you go; tennis ball in there.
That's really going to help me, because when I am going to be serving I am going to be serving with two balls, because you have a first serve and a second serve.
You don't want to be leaving the ball on the floor because you can step on it and you don't want to be tossing with two balls in your hand because you're not going to have a good toss.
So, you want to make sure you have pants or a place where to put your balls.
That's concludes a little clip about balls.